# Pablo Uboldi

### FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

I am a professional full-stack developer with experience working in Python, Django, Flask, Databases, HTML, CSS/Bootstrap, React, JavaScript, and TypeScript. I am a fast learner and a self-taught person - my previous job experiences have driven me to learn diverse specialized software, such as Mathematica, SolidWorks, AutoCAD, Simscale or Matlab.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Academic**

 Aerospace Engineer - National Technology University, 2021

#### **Courses**

- <u>CS50's Web Programming with Python and</u>
  <u>JavaScript Harvard, 2023</u>
- <u>Typescript: The Complete Developers Guid Udemy, 2023</u>
- The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp - Udemy, 2023
- 100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp for 2022 - Udemy, 2022

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Personal Website (06/2022 06/2022)
- To-do list Website (05/2022 05/2022)
- · Football Statistics Website (07/2022 08/2022)

#### **LANGUAGES**

- · Spanish Native
- English Proficient

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION



pabloauboldi@gmail.com



+44 7502058637



Post Code: SE9 6NN



github.com/pablouboldi



Right-to-Work

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Software Engineer**

Arena LLC, December 2022 - June 2023

Development of server-side software for:

- o Email notifications system
- O Ethereum Name Service recollection from blockchain addresses
- Client Tag filtering
- Activation funnel graph parameters

## **Software Engineer**

Freelance, July 2022 - present

- Integration of social and cryptocurrency profiles for analysis.
- O Development of a Discord Bot to collect user data.
- Web UX development for impact measurement in digital marketing campaigns, for a startup.
- Development of a Python script for solving Taylor-Maccoll equations for supersonic flow around a cone. For university

#### Fluid Mechanics Associate Professor

National Technology University, March 2018 - Present

- I oversee the theoretical and practical evaluation activities developed for the students of Aerospace Engineering.
- Class dictation.

#### **Project Manager**

Natural and Exact Sciences Faculty, UBA, March 2014 - August 2021

- I was part of the Technical Department, co-leading the electrical maintenance team for small and medium scale projects.
- I collaborated with the IT Department in software support and troubleshooting of staff's PCs.